（いの）んもう…。
Man, it's my day off,
任務なしのオフだっていうのに→
お使いを頼まれるなんて…。
so how'd I end up getting sent
on an errand ?
なに…　雷？
Was that lightning?
ウソ…　サクラ！？
No way! Is that Sakura?
（サクラ）うわぁ～！！
Sakura!
サクラ！！　ねえ　大丈夫なの！？
Hey, you okay? Sakura!
サクラ！！
Hang on! I'll get you down
in a second!
待ってなさい！
すぐ助けに行くから！
（綱手）見た感じ
たいした怪我ではなさそうだ。
骨も異常なし。　内臓も大丈夫。
From what I see,
it's nothing serious.
落ちた高さを考えれば→
わが弟子ながら
恐ろしく頑丈といえるだろう…。
Her bones are fine.
Internal organs too.
だが…。
Considering the heights
you fell from,
おい…　私がわかるか？
you're tough,
even for a student of mine.
え～っと…。
However…
（シズネ）体はともかく　頭ですね…。
Hey, do you know who I am?
Uh…?
綱手様　これって…。
It's not her body, but her head.
いわゆる
記憶喪失ってやつだろうな。
Lady Tsunade,
what's wrong with her?
やっぱり…。
She has amnesia.
でも　まあ　一時的なものですよね。
I knew it.
なんとも言いかねる。
いろいろな患者を診てきたが→
But it's temporary, right?
あまり　お目にかかる
症状じゃないからな。
It's hard to say.
I've had all sorts of patients,
じゃあ　最悪
このまんまってことも…？
but I haven't seen symptoms
like these before.
フッ…　大丈夫。　まだ１６歳だ。
You mean she might be
like this forever?
これからの人生のほうが→
Don't worry.
She's only 16 years old.
はるかに長…。
She has so much more of
her life ahead of her.
まあ　こっちも
文献を当たってみよう。
あとは　しばらく様子をみて…。
Anyway, I'll check the literature
on the condition.
ん？　何か思い出したのか？
Beyond that, we'll just need
to keep an eye on her.
これ　最初から
こんなんでしたっけ？
What're you doing?
どうも不自然というか…。
Were these like this
from the start?
最近になって
盛ったなんてことは…？
They seem so unnatural.
Did they get bigger just recently?
こ…　これは…
天からの授かりものだ～！
I was…
（サクラ）あ～！　痛い…。
blessed with these by Heaven!
綱手様　頭！
頭殴っちゃ駄目ですって！
O-Ouch!
Lady Tsunade, not her head!
You mustn't hit her head!
このショックで　治ることもある。
サクラは今　普通じゃないんです。
もっと　寛容に…。
Sometimes the shock will fix it.
Sakura isn't herself right now.
ねえ　サクラ。　大丈夫？
Try to go easy on her.
Sakura, are you okay?
貧乳…？
Underdeveloped…
（シズネ）標準サイズだ　こら～！
They're average!
（綱手）こら！　頭はよせ！
Hey! Not the head!
（いの）シズネ先輩
寛容に！　寛容に～！
Shizune, easy…easy!
ほんと　あんたってば
命知らずにも　程があるわよ。
You can only go so far with that
reckless fearlessness of yours.
おかげで　こっちまで
とばっちりじゃない。
Because of you,
I got caught in the crossfire.
ねえ　ほんとに
何も覚えてないの？
You really don't remember
a thing?
う～ん…　何となく
見覚えはあるというか…。
No.
This place looks vaguely familiar.
住んでいた里だってことは
わかるような…。
I sort of know that this is the village
where I used to live.
でも　それ以上は
モヤがかかった感じで…。
But beyond that,
everything is foggy.
家まで送ってあげるから。
I'll take you to your house.
しばらく
おとなしくしてるのね。
Behave yourself for a while.
って　おばさんたち　留守だし～！
Wouldn't you know it?
Nobody's home!
Good grief!
まいったなぁ…
こんな状態のサクラを→
I can't just leave Sakura here
in her condition.
放り出すわけにも
いかないじゃない…。
ねえ　いの。
ほんとに　ここが私の家…？
Hey, Ino?
Is this really my home?
Yes, it is.
Ever since you were born.
そうよ。　生まれてから今まで→
It's where you grew up.
ず～っと　あんたが育った家。
Since I was born?
生まれてから…？
Okay, let's go ask
you-know-who for help.
よし。　とりあえず
あいつを巻き込むか。
He's not home either!
って　こっちもいないし！
Where is he when
a friend needs him?
仲間がピンチだってのに
ほんと　使えない。
Ino, what is this place?
いの　ここって…。
It's the home of
your fellow teammate.
あんたと同じ班のやつの家よ。
You've been together forever,
so I thought this might
help you remember.
ずっと一緒の班だから→
なんか　思い出すきっかけに
なるかと思ったんだけど…。
What kind of person is he?
それってどんな人？
そうね…。
Well, let's see…
He's blonde, dopey-looking,
wears orange clothes,
金髪でアホ顔で　オレンジの服で→
forgetful, scatterbrained
and loves ramen.
忘れっぽくてバカで
おっちょこちょいで→
Ramen?
Did you remember something?
ラーメンが好きで…。
ラーメン！？
Is his name…
なんか思い出した？
もしかして
その人の名前って→
Char Siu [BBQ Pork]¸
Wakame [Kelp], Corn?
チャーシュー？　ワカメ？　コーン？
Nope.
違うな　えっと…。
Nitamago [Boiled Egg]?
You're so close…
It's Naruto.
あっ　煮卵！
微妙に　はずすわね…。
ってか　ナルトだけど。
Sorry, I felt like
I remembered something.
ごめん。
なんか　思い出せそうな
気がしたんだけど。
That's okay.
It won't come back all at once.
Another person you've known
a long time would be…
まあ　そう
うまくはいかないか。
Sasuke.
あと　あんたと
つきあい長いのは…。
Sasuke?
He's not here in the village
right now, but…
サスケ君かな。
サスケ君？
He's a totally cool guy with black hair
and good looks,
今は　諸事情で
里にいないんだけど→
and on top of that, he's…
いつもクールで
びしっと黒髪のイケメンで→
A playboy?
Huh?
Why'd I say that?
おまけに…。
チャラ男。
I had this powerful image
in my mind just now.
え？
What the—?
あれ？　なんだろう。
今　ものすごくそんなイメージが→
If this is her reaction to Sasuke…
パーッと浮かんで　あれ？
It's pretty serious.
《サスケ君にまでこの反応じゃあ
相当　重症だわ》
Sakura!
I will make you better,
I promise!
サクラ　あんたのことは
私が絶対に治してあげるから！
Really?
It's the first time I've ever
seen someone with amnesia!
（シカマル）マジかよ　記憶喪失の
やつなんか初めて見たぜ。
Did she forget me too?
Stupid question.
You're the first one she'd forget!
（シノ）俺のことも忘れたのか？
（キバ）愚問だな。
This is horrible!
The bittersweet days
of our youth…gone!
むしろ
真っ先に忘れるだろ。
（リー）ひどい話です。
That's so cruel!
僕たちの甘酸っぱくて
ほろ苦い青春の日々が→
We were together?
すべて消え去ってしまったとは！
Ignore him.
残酷すぎます！
He's like "that," you know.
（サクラ）私たち　そんな日々を？
（テンテン）気にしないで。
So, how is she?
Will she get better?
ちょっと　あいつ
あれなところがあるから。
Lady Tsunade said
she'd do some research.
で？　どうなんだよ。
治りそうなのか？
But worst case,
Sakura might stay this way.
That's not good.
綱手様も
調べてみるって言ってたけど→
Right!
This is when we, as friends,
have to help her!
最悪　このままの可能性も…。
（ヒナタ）そ　そんなの駄目だよ。
C'mon, do you remember
anything at all?
そうよね　こんなときこそ→
We'll help you all we can!
仲間の私たちが助けないと！
It's like I remember all
of you, but…
ねぇ　なんでもいいから
覚えてることはない？
not quite the important things.
私たち
できる限り協力するから！
What does that mean?
みんなのことは
覚えてるような…。
Well, she seems pretty confused.
でも　肝心なところが
違うような…。
Poor Sakura…
どういう意味？
Okay then,
here's what we'll do.
それが　いろいろ
混乱もしてるみたいで。
What if we all matched ourselves
to Sakura's memories?
サクラさん　かわいそうに…。
So well, we all agreed, but…
じゃあ　こうしましょ。
みんなで　サクラの記憶に
合わせてみるっていうのは？
I'm the Hidden Leaf's top
canine handler.
（キバ）とまあ…　一応
賛成はしたけどよ…。
I realize this is for a friend,
but getting demoted to a cat handler?
木ノ葉きっての犬派の俺が→
仲間のためとはいえ
猫派の軍門に下るとは…。
I never imagined I'd face
such psychological torture.
（赤丸）クーン…。
Hang in there, Shino.
We're all in the same boat.
あ～っ！！
まさか　これほどの
精神的攻撃を受けるとは…。
But we're doing this for Sakura.
Hinata… Poor thing.
（ヒナタ）しっかりして　シノ君。
みんな同じだよ。
But why are we separated
from everyone else
でも　サクラさんのためだもん。
and tied up tightly like this to boot?!
（ネジ）ヒナタ様　お気の毒に…。
I don't know.
Apparently we,
especially you, Neji,
それにしても　なんで俺たちは
みんなからこんなに離れて→
give Sakura the chills
if we're near her.
What have I ever done?
This is absolutely outrageous.
おまけに　ガチガチに
拘束されているんだ！
わかりません。
なんでも僕たち→
Sorry about this, Neji.
But we were asked to do this.
特に　ネジがそばにいると
サクラさんは悪寒がするそうで。
It's mortifying.
俺が何をした！
まったく　心外極まる。
Now what were these two like?
ごめんね　ネジ。
これも要望だから。
Hey, Ino.
Is this really going to help her
regain her memory?
無念…。
Everybody's looking pretty weird.
（サクラ）う～ん　この２人は
どんなだったかな…。
But if this helps her regain
her memory, it'll be worth it.
おい　いの。
本当にこんなのが→
So be a good sport
and go along with it.
Got it! Choji, put this on!
記憶を戻す
手助けになんのか？
（チョウジ）みんな
変なことになってるような。
But this is… What's going on?
でも　これで記憶が戻れば
儲けものなんだし→
And Shikamaru…
Sorry to do this,
but would you act sort of stupid?
おとなしく　つきあいなさい。
うん！
チョウジは　これつけて。
Huh? Why me?
With a smile, if you can.
Come on, Shikamaru!
これって　どういう意味？
I don't get it.
I feel like my memory is
just about to clear up, but…
それと　シカマル！　悪いけど→
You tried hard.
It's all you could do…
ここからは
バカっぽい感じでいてくれる？
はぁ？　俺がなんで？
But it feels sort of strange,
you know.
できれば　笑顔で。
Like, why did I suddenly
show up there?
ほら　シカマル！
And I can vaguely remember
everyone in the village, and yet…
わ～い　やっほ～。
It's just this house that
I totally can't remember.
It's as though…
I'm coming here for the first time.
What is it?
If it isn't Ino…
Glad we caught you!
Auntie, Uncle, where were you?
They were having a sale
across the bridge,
おかしいなぁ。
so we ended up buying too much.
なんか　こう　もう少しで→
But we got the spoils!
モヤが晴れそうな
気がしたんだけど。
These things were heavy,
and it was a long trip,
努力は　したんだし
しようがないって。
but we can't let
good spoils spoil, right?
でも　なんか
いろいろ気持悪いのよね。
Get it?
Something bad happened…
なんで　私　いきなり
あんな所に現れたんだろう？
What is it?
Was there a battle?
それにね
里のことも　みんなのことも→
Well, a bath'll  help you forget!
That's enough already!
ぼんやりだけど覚えてるのに→
Look, you're scaring Ino away!
この家のことだけは
まったく覚えてないの。
Your parents are as intense as ever.
まるで
初めて来た場所みたいに…。
But now that they're back,
I don't have to…
どうしたの？
（メブキ）あら　いのちゃん！
Why?
Huh?
よかった！　おじさん　おばさん
どこ行ってたんですか？
Sakura?
（メブキ）今日　橋の向こうの商店街が
特売日で→
ついつい買い過ぎちゃって。
Why're you crying?
（キザシ）でもって　これが戦利品。
I don't know.
The moment I saw them, I…
重たかったし遠かったけど→
千里の道も一歩から。
なんつって　なんつって！
I'm sorry!
Hey! Where're you going?!
What's going on with those two?
いや　それより　大変なことが…。
You don't think my jokes
were too much for her?!
なんだ？　戦闘でも起こったか？
そんなもの
銭湯に行って忘れてしまえ！！
I see, I see…
ハハハハ！
いいかげん　しつこいわよ！
Huh?
ほら　いのちゃんが
ドン引きしてるじゃない。
相変わらず強烈ね。　あんたの両親。
Hey, wait up!
Sakura! Sakura, c'mon!
でも　まぁ　親が戻ってくれば
私も安心して…。
なんで？
え？
Listen, I don't know
what made you cry,
サクラ？
but why'd you run away?!
Did you hear me?
って　ええ～？
どうして泣くのよ？
I don't know.
But it hurts bad right here.
わからない。
なんか　２人を見たら…。
I really don't know
what came over me.
ごめん！
って　ねえ！
Anyway, we can't leave things
as they are.
どこ行くのよ！
あの子たち
どうしちゃったのかしら？
Let's go back.
I could stay with you if you'd like,
until you calm down.
まさか
俺のダジャレが感動的すぎて…。
Ino…
そうか　そうか。
あぁ…。
It's gone…
ん？
Huh?
My pendant!
Pendant?
もう　待ちなさいよ！
Come to think of it,
サクラ！　サクラってば！
you were wearing some jewelry
I'd never seen you with before.
ハァ…　ハァ…　ハァ…。
How could this happen?!
I've never ever taken it off!
It's something I mustn't ever lose!
あんたさ
泣くのもわかんないけど→
Sakura?
いったい　なんで逃げるの？
Oh…
There you are!
Auntie! Uncle!
ねぇ　聞いてる？
わからない。
I've had enough.
You ran all the way here
at top speed…
ただ　胸が痛くて　苦しくて…。
ほんと
どうしちゃったんだろう？
Sakura, are you looking
for something?
でも　このままってわけには
いかないでしょ。
You're at that age
where you lose things.
帰ろう。
なんなら　あんたが落ち着くまで
一緒にいてもいいし。
Oh dear, it's not like you to
not needle Dad and his bad jokes.
いの…。
Apparently, it was
very important to her.
I see.
Was it this that you lost?
You dropped it in front
of the house earlier.
Surprised me, though.
It's exactly like the one I have.
Reporting.
Our third line of defense has…
I see…
Sakura!
Thank you again.
Don't mention it.
Your parents helped me a lot.
Here…
Buying the same thing—
like father, like daughter.
ない！
え？
私のペンダント！
This time, be careful not to drop it.
ペンダント？
そういえば　あんた　今日は
見慣れないアクセ　付けてたわよね。
So that's what's happening.
C'mon, we chased after you.
Don't you have something to say?
そんな…　ずっと
離したことなんかないんだから！
絶対に　なくしちゃいけないのに！
Uncle, Auntie, you see,
Sakura's not…
サクラ？
おお！
What's that for?!
いたいた！
おじさん　おばさん！
Thank you…
もう　嫌になっちゃう。
こんなとこまで
全力で　かっ飛ばすんだから。
C'mon now, it's nothing to
get all teary about.
Sakura's losing it?
サクラ　何か探してんのか？
It's because I'm so happy.
落とし物なお年頃…。
I love you both!
なんちってな！　ヘヘヘヘ！
あら　あんたが　お父さんに
突っ込まないなんて珍しいわね。
Be sure to come home
by suppertime!
それが
大事なものだったみたいで。
I don't know what
just happened, but…
なるほどな～。
I assume you remember everything?
なぁ
お前の落としたものって　これか？
あっ！
Yes, everything, finally…
さっき　家の前で
落としていったんだろう。
Then tell me…
Why'd you fall from there?
That day,
でも　驚いたぞ～。
俺のやつと
まったく同じなんだからな～。
I was dispatched with
orders from Lady Hokage.
Okay, it's just ahead.
I don't know what it was.
Just that a powerful force
reeled me in.
And when I came to,
I found myself in this world.
えっ！？
♪～
I'm probably not
the Sakura you know.
I'm not from here…
This world, you say…
((報告します。
第三防衛ラインは　もう…。
I guess your memory's still affected.
Ino!
Don't worry.
そうか…。
I'll stay with you for the long haul.
♪～
I'll even study the literature
on amnesia!
What the—?!
Sakura? You're…
Ino…
Thank you…
for being my friend here, as well.
Huh?
What're you talking about?
Hey!
She just faded away?
サクラちゃん！
What just happened?
わぁ～！　いつも　すみません。
いいのよ～。
Was it a Summoning?
But I don't see any jutsu formulas.
(あんたの両親にはね…))
I'm probably not
the Sakura you know…
♪～
Impossible…
If that's true…
Where did the Sakura I know go?!
ほら。
NINJA NETWORK NEWS
Ninja Network News!
同じものを買うなんて
やっぱ　親子なのね～。
Good evening,
I'm Mabui from the Cloud.
今度は
落とさないように気をつけろよ。
I'm Shikaku Nara.
On the first day since the outbreak
of the Fourth Great Ninja War,
そうだったんだ…。
various campaigns are unfolding.
こら　サクラ　わざわざ
追っかけてきたんだから→
The battlefields are split
into three main groups.
何か言うこと
あるんじゃないの？
Darui's First Company and
Kitsuchi's Second Company
あのね　おじさん　おばさん
今　サクラは…。
are deployed to the Coastal Front.
Gaara's Fourth Company is facing
the late Kage in the Desert Front.
うぉ～っ！
ちょっと　なに～！？
ありがとう…。
Kakashi's Third Company and
the Seven Ninja Swordsmen
of the Mist
are engaged in the Frontline.
もう
泣くほどのことじゃないでしょ。
Mifune's Fifth Company is en route to
provide support for the Commando Unit.
サクラが　錯乱？
Late breaking news:
On the Coastal Front,
だって…　なんだか嬉しくて…。
the formidable enemies Kinkaku and
Ginkaku have been successfully sealed.
２人とも　大好き！
Now, for a live report from the scene.
Samui, from the First Company!
Oh, it seems Darui is
on camera right now.
（メブキ）ご飯までには帰りなさいよ！
It seems we don't have any audio.
なんか
よく　わかんないんだけど→
What happened to Samui?
とにかく　思い出したってことで
いいのよね？
Well, let's go back to the Desert front.
The enemies are
the Second Mizukage,
the Second Tsuchikage,
the Fourth Kazekage,
the Third Raikage…
うん　やっと全部…。
じゃあ　教えて。
To be honest,
it's hard for us to make
a connection between them.
なんで
あんな所から落ちてきたの？
They all come from
different time periods.
あの日→
Let's try to go on scene.
私は　火影様から
伝令の任務を受けていて…。
Temari from the Fourth Company?
Temari?
((よし　この先ね。
The Desert Front is definitely
engulfed in a sandstorm.
んっ？
(えっ！？　うわっ！　うわ～っ！))
I wonder how the Frontline
is doing?
私にも　わからない。
The Third Company has succeeded
in sealing Zabuza Momochi,
ただ　強い力に引き込まれて
気がついたら　ここにいたの。
one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist,
as well as his subordinate.
私は　たぶん
あなたの知ってるサクラじゃない。
Tajiki, who's on scene? Tajiki?
この世界の人間じゃないの。
We can't seem to get
a hold of Tajiki.
この世界ねえ…。
Onto the issue at hand in
this Fourth Great Ninja War.
やっぱ　記憶は
あれなままなのね…。
The Jinchuriki of the Eight Tails and
the Nine Tails, Lord Bee and Naruto.
いの！
心配しないで。
ちゃんと
気長に　つきあってあげる。
In order to hide from Madara,
文献も読んで　勉強するし！
they have been isolated
inside Turtle Is
えっ？
えっ　サクラ　あんた…。
いの…。
ありがとう。
こっちでも友達でいてくれて。
は？　あんた　なに言って…。
ちょっと！
は！　消えちゃった…。
なにこれ　口寄せ？
でも術式も何もないんだけど。
((私は　たぶん
あなたの知ってるサクラじゃない))
まさか　そんな…。
あれが　ほんとだとしたら→
私の知ってるサクラは…。
どこに行っちゃったのよ～！
皆様　お変わりございませんか？
美空ひばりです。
では　最後まで
ごゆっくり　お楽しみください。
（宮本）『木曜８時のコンサート
名曲！　にっぽんの歌』。